Deveesh Mehandiratta

Game Developer at Indroydlabs

Summary

I'm currently pursuing my engineering in Computer Science. I have been doing Android Development from 2 years and Game Development in Unity 3D from +1 year Having worked on projects in teams as well as alone, I have learned Adobe Photoshop at an Advanced Level to facilitate for the designing requirements for personal projects and Internships. I love learning new and powerful tools and exploring new interests.

Following is a link to one of my live Android projects:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=devapps.secretsandconfessions

Experience

Game Developer

January 2018 - Present

Indroyd Labs is a team of highly passionate people who make great games. I am fortunate to get a chance of working with them and develop games for clients of different industries. It is a work from home internship and everything is managed by call and emails.

Graphic Designer

January 2018 - March 2018 (3 months)

Igreenik is a team of very hardworking people. I did a work from home internship at Igreenik as a Graphic designer. I made designs for several purposes like company portfolio, visiting cards, logos for several clients, wallpapers etc. I also did image editing using Adobe Photoshop. It was a pleasure working at Igreenik.

Android Developer at Daphnis Labs

June 2017 - August 2017 (3 months)

Graphic Designer

November 2016 - January 2017 (3 months)

I made several Wrapping paper designs for this Work from home internship at JK Offset.

Education

Bharati Vidyapeeth Deemed University

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Engineering, 2015 - 2019

Deveesh Mehandiratta

Game Developer at Indroydlabs



Contact Deveesh on LinkedIn